aglr.com 2016-10-15

# AGL Resources - Privacy Policy

Terms of Service | Privacy Policy | Stock Quote Disclaimer

**Privacy Policy**

We respect your privacy and are committed to keeping confidential any personal information you share with us. Please read this privacy policy statement carefully. It covers the collection, use, disclosure, and protection of information that we collect about individuals through this website. This statement does not apply to those of our websites or portions of our websites that do not display or link to this privacy policy statement or that have their own privacy policy statement. 

We reserve the right to update this statement at any time and in any manner. We will provide notice of any changes by posting the revised policy to the applicable websites. We encourage you to periodically review this policy to be informed of our privacy practices. At any time, the currently-posted statement shall govern. 

**Why do we collect information?**  
We collect your information because it enables us to give you, and our other customers, convenient access to certain features and services. It also enables us to verify your identity in our interactions with you, provide you with a consistent and personalized experience, and deliver a superior level of customer service. For example, to access certain of our features, services, and other non-public areas of our website, you will be asked to sign in with a login name and password. If you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you will not be able to access such non-public areas because we cannot verify your identity. Your information also helps us keep you posted on status updates, reminders, confirmations, and special offers, and events that may interest you. 

**What is “personal information”?**  
For purposes of this statement, "personal information" includes private information collected by us that may be used to uniquely identify an individual. Personal information does not include any public information about an individual that is available through federal, state, or local public records. It also does not include any information that, by itself, does not uniquely identify an individual, such as raw data aggregated across many individuals. 

**Collecting and Using Information.**  
Unless we say otherwise when collecting such information, we will use any personal information you provide to us in accordance with the terms of this statement. We will collect, use, and retain your personal information only to the extent reasonably necessary, and for the purposes we describe to you in this statement or elsewhere. Such purposes include in connection with our provision of requested services to you and our other customers, and the operation and administration of this website. 

We may combine information we collect about you from this website with information we obtain about you from other sources, including aggregate data from third parties. For purposes of research and analysis, we may also aggregate personal and other information about you with information about our other customers. You agree to such use and agree that we will retain complete ownership and control over any aggregate data that we compile or acquire. 

Further, you also agree that we may use your information to communicate status updates, reminders, confirmations, and other messages to you related to your purchase of our products and services, or use of the features and services on our websites. We may also use your information, where we have obtained your permission to do so, to communicate special offers and promotions from us, our affiliates, and our marketing partners that may interest you. 

Sometimes we hire other companies to provide products and services to you on our behalf, such as processing transactions, hosting websites, conducting customer surveys, and providing customer service. We may share some of your personal information with these companies to enable them to perform such work. These companies are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose and are required to maintain its confidentiality. 

We may also share your personal information with our parent and affiliated companies for their use in compliance with this statement. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties where we have obtained your permission to do so and where we are required or permitted to do so by law. We will not sell your personal information to third parties without your prior permission. 

**Technical Information and Cookies**  
As is true of most websites, we gather technical information about your interaction with our website automatically, and store it in our logs. Such information includes Internet Protocol addresses, web browser type, Internet Service Provider, referring or exit pages, operating system, and date and time stamps. 

And, as is true of most websites, we use “cookies” – small text files that are stored on your computer that allow our web site to identify your browser, session and your customized preferences from one visit to the next. You may configure your web browser to accept or decline cookies from our website. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to login to use certain private areas of our website. We also will not be able to customize your experience or deliver certain interactive services and features to you. 

By way of example, we may use technical information and cookies 

> **a.** to provide you with a more customized experience on our website and provide you greater convenience each time you interact with us,   
>  **b.** to help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular and how much time our users spend in each,   
>  **c.** to measure the effectiveness of our customer communications and the searches performed on our website,   
>  **d.** to administer our website,   
>  **e.** to study traffic patterns and trends on our website, and   
>  **f.** to study aggregate demographic information about our users as a whole.

How can you access the personal information we have collected about you?   
You may request a copy of the personal information that we currently hold about you by sending a detailed email to [ privacy@aglresources.com ](mailto:privacy@aglresources.com) with all specifics necessary for us to consider and respond to your request. 

**How do we protect the information we have collected about you?**  
We take a number of technical and procedural precautions to protect your personal information from misuse and unauthorized access or disclosure. For security reasons, only some of our safeguards are described below and only in general terms. 

To safeguard your personal information, we 

> **a.** monitor user accounts and suspend or delete accounts that have been inactive for excessive time lengths,   
>  **b.** use secure sockets layer (SSL) encryption to collect and transmit personal information you communicate with us electronically,   
>  **c.** require passwords for company website access and email access to non-public areas of the website and mask such passwords through visual encryption, and   
>  **d.** limit administrative access to active user logins and passwords and new user account setups.

You can also help us protect your personal information by 

> **a.** using only secure web browsers,   
>  **b.** employing common anti-virus and anti-malware tools on your system to keep it safe,   
>  **c.** as applicable, carefully logging out after using our website,   
>  **d.** as applicable, using strong passwords with a combination of letters and numbers,   
>  **e.** as applicable, changing your password often, and   
>  **f.** as applicable, notifying us by email at [ privacy@aglresources.com ](mailto:privacy@aglresources.com) if you feel your login and/or password have been compromised.

Finally, please exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. We may provide public areas on our website where you can post information about yourself and others. We do not control who reads postings on our website, or how they may use or disclose such information. If you choose to voluntarily disclose personal information on public portions of our website, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. 

**Disclaimer as to other Websites.**  
This website may contain links to third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and specifically disclaim any such responsibility. You are responsible for knowing when you are leaving our website to visit a third party website, and for reading and understanding the terms of use and privacy policy statements for each such third party website. 

**Special Statement for Career Applicants.**  
Any personal information you provide us when applying for a career position with our company will be used solely to consider and act upon your application. We may retain your personal information for a period of time, but only for as long as necessary for such purposes. We may disclose your personal information to our subsidiaries, affiliates, and agents for the purpose of evaluating your qualifications for the particular position you applied for, or other available positions. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties hired by us to collect, maintain, and analyze candidates for career positions. 

**How can you contact us?**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy statement, please email us at [ privacy@aglresources.com ](mailto:privacy@aglresources.com). You can also reach us by regular mail or fax at: 

Privacy Officer  
AGL Resources Inc.  
Ten Peachtree Place, Location #1470  
Atlanta, GA 30309  
Fax: 404-584-3714 

**Terms of Use.**  
Please read our Terms of Use statement to understand the terms applicable to your use of this website. By using this website, you acknowledge that you have read our terms of use, as well as this privacy policy statement, and agree to comply with all terms. 

Back to Top
